let str = `[{"question":"A%3A%20Did%20you%20inform%20his%20secretary%20for%20the%20appointment%20cancellation%3F%0AB%3A%20No%2C_____________%0AA%3A%20Of%20course%2C%20it's%20necessary%20to%20call%20them%20and%20confirm%20about%20the%20cancellation.","type":"choice","solve":"3","answers":["I%20wouldn't","I%20shouldn't","I%20don't%20feel%20like%20it","Should%20l%3F"]},{"question":"A%3A%20I%20think%20I%20will%20purchase%20a%20new%20book%20within%20this%20week.%20I%20can't%20wait%20for%20reading%20its%20new%20episode.%0AB%3A%20What%3F%20Yesterday%20you%20were%20just%20complaining%20that%20you%20have%20been_____________________.","type":"choice","solve":"1","answers":["on%20and%20off","down%20and%20out","back%20and%20forth","up%20and%20away"]},{"question":"A%3A%20____________________________________%0AB%3A%20Well%2C%20I%20could%20show%20you%20another%20one.","type":"choice","solve":"2","answers":["The%20clients%20are%20looking%20for%20a%20new%20car.","Look%20at%20this%20car%2C%20isn't%20that%20good%3F","I'm%20afraid%20this%20one%20will%20one%20will%20never%20do.","Do%20you%20have%20any%20new%20car%20models%3F%20"]},{"question":"A%3A%20____________________________________%0AB%3A%20Most%20shops%20usually%20open%20at%208.30%20a.m.%20and%20close%20at%20p.m.%0AA%3A%20Brilliant!%20So%20I%20could%20go%20shopping%20after%20school.","type":"choice","solve":"0","answers":["What%20is%20the%20opening%20hour%20of%20the%20shops%3F","What%20time%20should%20I%20go%20shopping%3F","When%20I%20can%20go%20shopping%3F","Do%20the%20shops%20open%20in%20early%20morning%3F"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"2","answers":["remedy","therapy","meditate","antidote"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"1","answers":["derive","deprive","stem","originate"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"3","answers":["outstanding","renowned","celebrated","notorious"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"0","answers":["disable","discriminate","distinguish","differentiate"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"1","answers":["relate","seclude","associate","connect"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"1","answers":["enormous","prelude","gigantic","vast"]},{"question":"Three%20of%20the%20words%20in%20each%20group%20relate%20to%20one%20another%20in%20their%20meaning.%20Choose%20on%20word%20that%20does%20not%20belong.","type":"choice","solve":"2","answers":["distribute","provide","depend","offer"]}]`;

export default JSON.parse(str);
